fieldsupply.com 2016-12-05

# Field Supply - Privacy Policy | Field Supply

At Field Supply we are the white hats, the good guys, the Dudley Do-Rights saving the damsel in distress. We believe in God, Family, Country, Corps, and enjoy cheap laughs, quality products, and killer prices. We want you to buy with confidence. We've been doing this kind of thing for 20 years and sincerely appreciate the trust you place in us and all Brandshopper sites.  We are committed to respecting your privacy and securing your personal information. We collect certain bits of information to do some basic things: ship your packages, let you enjoy our site features and offers, and improve our products and customer service.

## Or, as our expensive lawyers with the fancy suits put it:

By visiting **FieldSupply.com** , you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy so please take a moment to review and understand the measures we take to protect you and the information you share with us. Questions and concerns should be directed to:

  * **FieldSupply.com** , a Brandshopper, LP company
  * 6771 Chrisphalt Drive
  * Bath, PA 18014
  * (800) 509-1169

## Information Collected

Our goal is to provide you with the best possible shopping experience and 100% satisfaction of any order you've placed with us. We collect and store information you enter on our website (such as name, address, telephone number, credit card information, email, etc.) to process your order, sign up for email offers and provide exceptional customer service.

## Use of information we collect

We engage third parties to perform services in connection with the operation of our business. These may include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing and promotional material distribution, Web site evaluation, data analysis and data cleansing. We provide Personal Information to these third parties, but authorize them to use this information only in connection with the services they perform.

**Partners:**  Brandshopper, LP partners with companies that offer products and services we believe may be of interest to our customers. if you purchase a product from us, there is a chance we may exchange your name with another company whose products and services might interest you. If you don not want your name exchanged, contact us at any time.

**DAA/DMA Standards:**  Our company and our trusted third parties may share with one another anonymous versions of user information collected at this site. We may use that information to link to and issue anonymous cookies containing demographic or intent-based data for online behavioral advertising purposes. Such cookies do not contain personally identifiable information. If you would like to opt out of online behavioral advertising, click on one of these links: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> or <http://networkadvertising.org/choices>.

## Cookies and Tags

A cookie is a small data file stored by your Web browser on your computer and is used to identify how you arrived at FieldSupply.com and stores information about your shopping cart. These cookies enable you to place an order on our Web site and allow us to enhance and personalize your shopping experience. Cookies never contain credit card information, are stored locally on your computer, and are only read by us at Brandshopper. In addition, we use cookies to remember items in your shopping cart and remember you when you return to our site.

If you set your browser to refuse cookies, please contact us at (800) 509-1169 to place your order.

In addition, pixel tags (which are simply tiny graphic images) are used to tell us what part of the site you have visited and to measure the effectiveness of searches and marketing efforts on our site. At times we may use a third party to perform these services, however they are prohibited from sharing or using this information with anyone except Brandshopper.

## Notification of Changes

Future changes to this Privacy Policy may be made at any time by sending you an email or posting notice of the changes on the site. Contact us at any time with questions.

Last updated: October 8, 2014
